7:00 p.m. or
Thank you for watching today.
We plan to have more people come next time.
Thank you very much.
It has begun.
Yes, ma'am.
Pleased to meet you.
please.
Thank you very much.
Good bye.
It's a new Sunday.
He's wearing a mask.
It's not a mask. My glasses are smudged.
I'll be the first one to wipe them off.
I'll wipe them off for you.
You can just throw that away.
That's cool.
Oh, wow, it's starting.
That's great, and that's great, and that's great, and that's great, and that's great, and that's great, and that's great, and that's great, and that's great.
So, good evening everyone.
I'm Shift Hanamichi, this week, please.
It's been a while since I've made my debut in the museum... a very long time. I've seen you at live concerts and such.
I've seen you at live concerts and such, but I thought you've grown up a bit.
I mean, she's got a bit of a curvaceous look. - Really?
Is this a service shot?
Wow!
Wow, that's a long time to pay.
It's a very long time!
And by the way... of course, you and Ebituu-chan...
Goods! EBITCHU-like goods!Goods! Ebichu-like goods!
66 and more! For example, acrylic stands and more recently...
I know there are towels and stuff, but can I ask you a fundamental question?
Do you have anything? It's the real root of it.
So if we make EBITCHU merchandise... people don't want it...
What is it that people are looking for now? For example, you have EBITCHU and SABON, right?
I've made towels and acrylic stands with this, of course.
I just received a message from Pee asking for advice, so if you have any ideas, I'd like to hear them.
I'd love to hear your ideas, but before that, how about some hanami shis (cherry blossom viewing gifts)?
I see. How about earrings?
It's a bit steep, but...
Are you a Kanai Devil? Kannai Devil.
I see... Kannai and Devil. Kannai on the right, Devil on the left...
Devil's left, DeVille's left, maybe... Pierce.
We usually don't mind if she wears earrings, but if I wear earrings, I'll be in trouble.
What? Do they look good on you? It's not something you get used to.
Are you used to it? How's the color? A little different?
I see... I see... first of all, I like the earrings.
What do you think of Sarpon? I mean, you know, when I think of "Cannai Devil", I think of drawing, you know, those random stickers.
Random stickers...
For example, these mysterious stickers.
That's right.
We all draw Gundams and other things, don't we?
EBITCHU Gundam, yes, that's right
Let's make stickers of that kind of thing.
I like to put them on my cell phone.
That's a good idea!
But we definitely shouldn't draw a Gundam.
I know... it's a no-no for the photographer, too.
I'm just saying "Gundam," but I can't draw a Gundam.He's just saying "Gundam," but I'm pretty sure he can't draw a Gundam.
If that's the case, I'd like to have a company-to-company talk with him.
I see.
I don't know what's going on.
What's that? The kind of thing everyone wants?
I want to make ramen.
Like bagged noodles.
Even in a cup?
Why not?
Of course it's tonkotsu (pork bone) ramen.
I'll make it under my supervision.
It's really good.
It's like, "This is good.
I'll just make it really cheap.
I'm going to lower the price to the limit.
Then, please let people eat more and more.
Wow, that's great!
That kind of thing is really good.
Don't you want to produce cup noodles?
I'd love to!
I want to!
Of course, it's a kind of collaboration.
in the world.
I'd like to try it once.
It's a dream, isn't it?
I'm just talking about my dream.
If there is anything you want, please let me know.
I'm sure you'll find what you're looking for.
For exampleFor example
Axta T-shirts
Hoodies
Penlight with voice
What's that?
It's a penlight with a voice.
You press a button on the penlight and someone's voice comes on.
"Come here!" or something like that.
I see.
Or an acrylic key chain.
Acrylic key chains?
The ones made of acrylic keychains.
Random badges.
Goods for the press.
That's right.
I see.
I'd like something with a costume motif of the part-timers.
Something like this.
Like this.
The price might be a little high, but...
But the general public can wear them, too.
Girls can wear it, and guys can wear it.
That's right.
They're very popular.
It's cute.
It's cute, isn't it?
It's really cute.
How about something like that?
How about a stuffed animal?How about a stuffed animal?
Plush?
Plushie?
Wait a minute.
Do you call stuffed toys "plushies"?
Don't you call them "plushies"?
Is that a professional term?
Yes, it is.
Nui.
I've never heard of it.
What's that?
It's some kind of Inu word, like "God"? That's...
Nui.
It's more like "nooi".
It sounds like a god.
His name is...
Maybe it's a cute stuffed animal.
I want a tote bag!
You're right.
I thought tote bags were the flat ones?
Yes, they are.
You know, the kind you sling over your shoulder.
That's for sure.
If it's okay to say anything else...
How about issuing a bill or something?
What?
Money.Money.
Like some kind of portrait of me.
Money I can't spend.
I can't spend it... not at all.
You're right.
Like bills.
Cars and stuff.
A car.
The cost is a big deal.
Like one car only.
One car only
It's really expensive.
I think it'll cost about 30 million yen if it's a limited edition.
That's great.
I love it.
An alarm clock.
It's like they wake you up
It's like waking us up with our own voice.
Yeah, you might want to wake up to the Master's voice.
Really?
Who's up for that?
He'll wake up... in one hit.
Yes, sir! That's how it is.
Out of the blue...
I didn't like it at all.
At 7 o'clock...
Really?
I don't like it.
Really?Seriously?
That's amazing.
That's seriously awesome.
Yeah.
Time to eat.
I see what you mean.
That's good.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's that, too.
And what else?
I'd like to ask you two more questions.
I'd like to ask you...
What is it that you want?
What you want?
What I want.
I wonder.
Well...
I guess I want something I can wear, but I think jewelry would be great.
If there were T-shirts, I'd buy them as merchandise. T-shirts?
Then there's the design... Earphones, headphones...
How about this picture on a T-shirt, where Sarpon draws the faces of all the Ebiju girls, me, and Sarpon?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
But you know, fans want that kind of thing, right?
Then you should draw Mr. Ebiju. No, I don't want to draw him.
Let me draw it. Let me draw it right now. What do you mean?
I'm naturally Yuichi Oda now.
Natural Yuichi Oda... You're in trouble.
Anyway... I guess you want something unique.
Oyama Festival T-shirt!
I wrote a song about a mountain called Daisen, and I thought it would be fun if a rock festival was held there.I wrote a song about a mountain called Mt. Daisen, and I thought it would be fun if they held a rock festival there.
I designed and made a T-shirt called "Daisen Rock Festival".
But I'm sure I'd want one of those. It's limited to 10 shirts.
I've already got the original, so it's fine if you want one right now.
I think it's easy to use a tumbler. Like a drinking cup.
I like the tumbler. It's a cute design.
So many things to choose from. So what do you guys do?
I wonder what's going on with Ebi-jyu-chan and the like lately. I see a lot of towels and stuff.
We put a hanger out once, with our face here, and hang it on the shoulder like this.
We took out a hanger. I guess something like that would be good.
Of course, something that's easy to use is fine, but something that's closely related to daily life but also a little different and unique would be the best.
I've heard that cup ramen is good. Cup ramen is also good. Let's make Devil Ramen.
Let's each make a cup ramen produced by, say, Hanamichi.
I want to make it. That sounds good.
I'd like to see what it tastes like. Cup ramen isn't expensive.
Well, maybe a little more expensive than usual.
I'm sure it'll be more expensive than normal, but...
I see some companies are looking at this.
Yes, please.
There's a museum around here, right?
Yes, there is.
I'm sure you'll pass by often.
I was wondering if you've seen it... or the President... or the President...
I'm sure he didn't see you... or the president... or the president... or the president... so it's all right for now.
So, by the way, since we're doing the Hanamichi shift today, let's do the flowers and see what the fellowships will be like in July.
July what fellowships shares jesteśmy bow to you
Yes, yes, yes...
Dre!
Yay!
Yay! Here you go! Thank you!Yay! Here you go! Thank you!
What is it? This time, I'm really happy!
Are you sure? Open it. Yay!
What's that? Have you seen this before? What's this?
Kimitamaido. What?
Wow! What is it? It's a cup!
It's a cup. Thank you!
Can I open it? Shall I open it?
Yes, open it.
Oh, wow! I'm so happy!
That's great, that's great, that's great, that's great, that's great.
Wow! It's so stylish! Stylish!
Yeah! Thank God!
What was that? Did you see the awesome footage?
I'm in, I'm in, I'm in. A mail-order show?
This is what you're trying to sell?
What? No, right? Oh, my God!
Why is there a nose and a nose and a nose? This is crazy.
Yuki-san says congratulations on your Hanamichi coming of age.
Oh! Thank you! That's right! I've become an adult!
Devil's Charge is here, and many other comments wishing you a happy birthday!
We have herbal tea.
Oh! I see... I see... You can put tea and other things in it and drink it.
Wow! I'm so happy! Thank you!
Yay! There's so much in here.
Is there anything in there yet?
It just came out.
Is that all of it?
What? You mean they're all in there?
Oh! Does it include the nose?Oh! Is there a nose in there?
No, I don't have a nose!
You have to go to the supermarket! It's not included!
Thank you!
Yes! That's great!
I'll see you in a little bit.
Congratulations! I'll leave them with you.
I had loose socks last year.
That's right! It's a gull!
I was wondering if you'd come up with something like that. I'm glad I did.
Easy to use! Thank you!
So! Well...
Thank you very much!
I'm number 18!
That means I'm an adult, right?
I'm an adult!
Wow!
You're an adult!
Isn't 18 too early to be an adult?
No, it's early!
Yes, it is!
From my point of view, 18 is still too young for me.
I was still slobbering and slobbering and slobbering.
I was slobbering and drooling.
So, 18, does that mean you'll have your coming-of-age ceremony next year?
Next year? Next year or the year after!
Yes, next year!
Thank you!
Congratulations.
Thank you very much!Thank you!!!
I'm so happy!
No, no, no, no, no, no.
That's why I'm here.
Let's get to the show.
Today is Friday on the air, so let's start the show!
Yes! I said, "Yes, sir." And now that it's Friday...
I think Hanamichi might want to talk about something.
It's Friday, isn't it? Friday is also a weekend.
What do you mean? What's going on? Something like...
What? How are things lately?
Lately? I'm doing really well.
What? I'm doing great.
You're in great shape? I'm in great shape.
I'm in great shape, I'm in great shape, I'm in great shape.
Good, good, good, good.
You're in great shape?
I'm in great shape. Really?
Yeah, I'm in great shape.
I'm really happy for you.
Can you say it more like Yuji Oda?
I'm doing great.
You look like him.
If you're watching the live broadcast, you should.
Yuji Oda has been amazing this week.
That's all I'm doing this week.
Yuji Oda is amazing!
They look so much alike.
You know...
You look like him.Looks like it.
I got the one with the big operation uniform that dances a little as a greeting.
I got it from the live feed guy.
There's no Rainbow Bridge blockade.
There's no Rainbow Bridge blockade now.
The second one from "The Movie".
I've already seen that one... back then... it was so much fun.
I've been watching "Odoru Dai Souzou Sensou" a lot.
Well, Yuichi Oda himself is watching it.
He's watching.
You look so much like him. No, seriously, you really do.
I'm surprised.
I don't need too long sentences.
If it's too long, it won't be similar.
One word is good.
It takes power to see it.
Well, well, well... So, give me a subject.
Let's start with your letter.
Well, by the way, we've got a quote.
That's great.
That's serious.
There's a girl named Cocona Sakuragi in Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku. Do you know her?
Oh, of course I do. She's cute, isn't she?
Oh, really?
Excuse me.
No, no, no, no.
I'll be right out.
Yes, they are. That's right. You think so too, Yuki Oda?
Cute.
It's interesting. This is interesting. Why this? It's interesting.Interesting. This is interesting. Why this? It's interesting.
I remember well the words of wisdom that Mr. Sakuragi said.
If you eat more than 15 raw oysters, you will feel sick.
No wonder!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
No, no, no, 14 is just barely okay.
So you are just barely okay.
But I love raw oysters. From the bottom of my heart.
But if I eat more than 15, I get really sick.
I see.
Well, well, then, it's a quote based on the Jikken.
It's the Jikko-ken.
No, I have never eaten more than five raw oysters at a time, by the way.
I've never eaten more than five raw oysters at a time.
Do you eat that many raw oysters?
Certainly.
I think it is quite a lot, so, in terms of kara-tsuke (dipping sauce), you can eat only about four oysters when they come out.
I have that image.
Then, how many oysters do you eat?
I went to many of them.
So you like it that much.
That's amazing.
It's definitely good, though.
Wow, it's amazing that it makes you feel sick.
It makes me sick.
It really makes me sick, more than 15 pieces.
I guess you're not going to break down somehow. You still have time.
If you push yourself, you might be able to do it, more.
If you push yourself, you might make it.
Well, well, well. That's how it is.Well, well, well. That's how it is.
Also, a word of wisdom.
I've got a lot of them.
Let's see, this one is amazing.
Ingrid Bergman, the actress.
She was quite a long time ago, wasn't she?
Yes.
Let's see, a little bit.
She was born in 1915 and died in 1982.
Wow.
Of course, I don't know much about her, but her name is really famous, and she won many Academy Awards and so on.
She's the one who won a lot of Academy Awards and so on.
Yes, he said that.
May I?
Kissing is a wonderful trick God devised to stop people from talking when they don't need words anymore.
Oh, wow.
Huh? Hey, hey, hey, Mr. Ogaki.
You don't get it, do you, Mr. Ogaki?
It didn't make sense.
I mean, it's a neat trick God came up with to stop us from talking when we don't need words anymore.
But it's definitely confusing.
I know.
Now that you mention it, it does seem a little strange.
What do you mean?
Kissing is God's way of stopping a conversation when words are no longer needed.
It's a neat trick.
What do you mean when you don't need the words anymore?
Isn't that what this is? We're not having this conversation anymore.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I don't think that's the kind of conversation you want to have.I don't think it's the kind of thing you do between people.
But it's deep.
Well, a little.
Thank you very much.
I don't understand what you're saying.
I don't understand what you're saying when you say it in a jumbled way.
I don't know what it means... that by kissing you, I don't need words.
So by kissing, you don't need words? You mean you don't need words? It's about conveying feelings, isn't it?
I see. So that's what it means. Is that right? That's what I'm getting at.
I've stopped talking. I'm trying to understand.
I don't need words.
It's just that it's in a different realm. It's amazing.
That's why...
So, the other day...
Well, the other day, as you're probably seeing, there was a rainbow.
There was a day when there was a rainbow, but there were a lot of clouds.
But there were a lot of clouds, so it didn't look like a rainbow, but I could see a part of it.
But I did see a part of it, so I call it a chocotte rainbow.
So this is what it looked like.
A little bit of rainbow. It would have been amazing if there were no clouds!
It was right at the clouds, but you could see it pretty clearly.
I was so surprised!
Wow, it's so beautiful!
A rainbow... a rainbow... yes...
Let me quote one more. This one's easy to understand.
This one is easy to understand... Fuji Soba? Fuji Soba is a standing-only noodle shop.
He's a man like this.
He's from Nagoya. I love standing-only noodle restaurants. I respect the founder a lot.
He said, "People are not stupid. They do the math.
Then I can't imagine running a business that doesn't have a place to live and doesn't pay people to work, a business that's considered a "black company".Then I can't imagine running a business that has no place to live, and if you don't pay me, I won't work for you. I can't imagine running a business that would be considered a "black business.
Thank you very much.
Isn't this nice?
It's easy to understand.
Thank you very much.
Yes, yes, yes.
Something like that.
Maybe...
Well, Fujisoba...
Especially wisteria soba.
When you get off at the station, it's like a wisteria soba dam
It's amazing!
By the way, only Enka (traditional Japanese folk song) is played in the restaurant.
I've been encouraged and healed by that enka song.
The first store opened in Shibuya.
The first store opened in Shibuya, but I heard it's a rule, but I think the founder thought so.
Well, I don't think the other restaurants only cater to banquets.
Amazing!
Nice...
Let's go there.
By the way, I'm that guy...
I grew up in Tokyo and hip-hop.
I'm making the most of it.
I call them my friends... but I wasn't born in Tokyo... when I said "ogya".
Where? I was born in Nagano Prefecture... in a place called Suwa City in Nagano Prefecture... by a lake called Suwa Lake.
I said "ogya" on the shore of a lake called Lake Suwa?
I said "edurai edurai" at that time, not "ogya" so don't cry "ogya"!
It's a well-known story that he said edulai edulai. I called my mom and told her it was true.
I called my mom and told her that's right... and she said it was called "Pripry" back then.
There's a lot of interesting stuff in there.There are many interesting things here.
Actually, there is a big lake called "Nest is a Lake", and the area around the lake is famous for eels.
Eels are very good!
Of course, the nest is good, but there is also Okaya in the next town, and that area is full of very good eels.
By the way, you went there?
The place of my birth.
1193 Takanami-ku, Yokohama City.
Eels! Wow! Looks delicious! It's huge!
Wow, this is great!
Like these eels... Yes, yes, yes...
There are a lot of eel shops, too.
And I didn't know...
I didn't know this 119 was eating eels or returning home, but there's a Skyline car near the birdhouse, and there's a Skyline Museum with all the skylines of the past. I don't know anything about it.
The first used car I bought after I got married was a Skyline (Model R 32)
I used to drive a 3030 too. It brings back memories.
30313233334... My first used car was an R30.
I'll be like this... with a camera.
I'm sure the Skyline is very rare and precious.
I'm sure you'll be able to see it live.
I love cars... and I drive them.
He's really like that... Oh, really?
I'm just saying boom, you get to ride in one of Dokin's cars, and there's like a carpet underneath, and it's really cool.
It's so cool. There's like a bunch of weird stuffed animals in there.
That's a long time ago. He's got a shifter that glitters.
I love it.
Gah!
It's about...
That's why there's a flower arrangement.
Dad, look, you drive.
He probably likes to drive.Maybe you love to drive.
Dad, I love to drive.
Tell him we're coming from Ibaraki.
From Ibaraki.
I thought it was a long way.
It is, isn't it?
It's so nice to see you.
Hello.
It's nice to meet you.
You look... really nice.
A little oblique, a little low-brow.
It's fun. It's fun. We can go to all kinds of places.
You know, from a Cervone point of view, what kind of car would you like to drive in the future?
If I had a lot of money, I'd like to drive an Aston Martin.
Aston Martin? A British car?
A foreign car? A foreign car.
James Bond, right? Left-hand drive.
And by the way, do you have any flowers for me? I don't care.
I want to drive Grandpa's Mercedes.
Grandpa drove a Mercedes? He must've been a real expert!
That's the Mercedes he drove back then!
You know, the one with the Mercedes logo like this?
And the headlights are a little rounded.
Oh my God! He's definitely the guy!
That's for sure.
He drove his grandpa's Mercedes! Oh, man!
That's awesome!
I was born in the 1940s or 1950s.
Oh, I see, but if you're aware of Hanamichi when you were born, then it must have been in the Heisei era or something.
It wasn't that long ago, was it?It wasn't that long ago.
That's what I thought.
Oh yeah, Mercedes-Benz, Mercedes-Benz, it's still a really nice car.
I think it's really nice, the comfort, the usability, it's great!
I think so! I've never driven one either.
I think it's great!
I hear other people's opinion.
So, when you say Mercedes Benz, it's like a luxury car, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
If it's worth the price, it's really great.
Mercedes is great, isn't it?
I wonder if he's seen it...
I wonder if the chairman of Mercedes has seen it...
I'd like a bench for my first car... my idol says so...
I'd love to have one.
It's not a Japanese car, so... but... it's just...
It's all backwards.
By the way, it's not a left-hand drive car.
It's the right side, and this side is the opposite.
The blinkers and that...
That's right.
That's our car, isn't it?
That's why I get confused when I rent a car and it's been a while since I've seen a domestic car.
I know exactly what you mean.
I was about to go around a traffic light when the windshield wipers went "wham!
Oh my God, I did it!
I wonder what they're going to do with the round numbers?
But when I was young, when I was in elementary school, there was a super car boom.But when I was young, when I was in elementary school, there was a super car boom.
You know, Lamborghinis, Heraris, Lamborghinis...
The roof was so low that you couldn't drive it, and the doors opened like this, and it had gull wings, and the lights were like waving.
And the lights came out like wings, and retractable lights...
I was a tiny kid back then and had no interest in cars, but I remember liking supercars, though I don't know why.
I remember I liked the Lamborghi Countach, the DeTomaso Pampera...
I mean, the name is so cool, like Lancia Stratos, it's such a cool name, it's so cool, it's got a huge impact.
Is a convertible a man's dream? Yes, but not really.
That's true, but I'm like that too.
I'd love to drive that supercar. It looks like it has a roof. Like a Helleri.
But... I think it's time...
I'm sorry, it's been a long story.
It's a long autumn night, right?
I'd like to say hello to the live audience.
Mwah! Hey!
I'm paying for it now! I'm watching! I'm watching you!
Please keep up the good work! Next week?
At 20:00! At 8pm! Next week at 8pm!
That makes it 7!
20:00! Please! Thank you very much!
Yes, we are done. Thank you very much.
And, well, you know what?
It's over.
Yes, it's over. So, by all means, even if it's just for the first time,
If you pass by Hanamichi, please tell your father or something,
Excuse me, I'd like to buy a small car.
After all, your father uses the car at home, right?
That's right. Of course I do.
So, you would like to have your own car, even if it is a mini car.
Well, yes.Oh no, that's right.
It's pretty cheap for a light car or something. Also, taxes are cheaper on light cars. Is that so? It's totally different.
Can I say something random? You know, the car I am driving now costs about 40,000 yen a year.
The car tax and the mini car tax are about 8,000 yen. The car tax and the mini car tax are about 8,000 yen. What? That's cheap! That's so cheap!
Was it around 10,000 yen now? They are cheap. So the maintenance cost is not that much anymore.
It doesn't cost that much. And the accuracy of the current criminal records is very good. Especially in the Japanese culture, what's wrong with the criminal?
The performance is so good that it's hard to believe it's a punishment. So why not just use it as a punishment? I often regret it.
I often regret it. It's amazing, isn't it?
I paid a shitload of money for a year. How many tens of thousands are you paying? Even if you don't do anything.
That's right. You know how much they charge you for car insurance?
I mean, how many tens of thousands of dollars do you pay for that alone?
Maintenance costs are very high. Maintenance costs are very high?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Well, well, well, well.
Well, let's see... like this.
Yes. There's something left to think about, isn't there?
Let's see. Do you have any regrets? Yes, I do.
Is there anything left to think about? Is this live distribution still going on?
The live feed is over. Oh, it's over.